{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1680,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":13,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"si1270","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4392","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_170","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_170","roles":{}},{"id":"Image_171","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_171","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Information Security Awareness Quiz Be Wi-Fi Wise! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_3","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_2","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19034","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Begin ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_106","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4365","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si4377","si4392","Image_170","Image_171","Text_Caption_2","Text_Caption_3","SmartShape_2","si19016","si19034","Text_Caption_106"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4365"}}},{"id":"Image_175","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_175","roles":{}},{"id":"si12441","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_338","roles":{}},{"id":"si12349","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_327","title":"1.  What is the best Wi-Fi router security? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_328","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12364","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_329","title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA)  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12360_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12382","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_332","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12386","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_333","title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12382_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wi-Fi Protected Access II (WPA2)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si20585","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20589","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20585_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si12435","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_337","roles":{}},{"id":"si12459","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_42","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_43","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19347","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19593","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19606","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19621","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19649","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19662","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19677","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19690","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide12483q0","for":"Slide12483q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_334","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is the oldest and increasingly vulnerable form of Wi-Fi encryption and should not be used.  Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) is improved but has been identified as being vulnerable to intrusion.  While nothing will ever be 100% secure (unless we refrain from using the technology), the next generation Wi-Fi Protected Access, WPA2, is currently the most secure choice.  Check the ‘wireless security’ or ‘wireless network’ settings page in your router’s administration console for your encryption type.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12417","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_335","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  Wired Equivalent Privacy (WEP) is the oldest and increasingly vulnerable form of Wi-Fi encryption and should not be used.  Wi-Fi Protected Access (WPA) is improved but has been identified as being vulnerable to intrusion.  While nothing will ever be 100% secure (unless we refrain from using the technology), the next generation Wi-Fi Protected Access, WPA2, is currently the most secure choice.  Check the ‘wireless security’ or ‘wireless network’ settings page in your router’s administration console for your encryption type.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si12429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_336","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide12483","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_175","si12349","si12364","si12386","si20589","si12459","si12473","si19347","si19361","si19593","si19606","si19621","si19634","si19649","si19662","si19677","si19690","si12429"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide12483"},"question":{"interactionId":"12329","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.  What is the best Wi-Fi router security?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_176","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_176","roles":{}},{"id":"si16169","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_580","roles":{}},{"id":"si16077","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_569","title":"2. What is a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_570","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16092","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_571","title":"Flooding a targeted network causing it to overload and shut down ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16088_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"322","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Flooding a targeted network causing it to overload and shut down\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16099","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_572","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16103","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_573","title":"A device that injects malware into the Wi-Fi network ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16099_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"324","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A device that injects malware into the Wi-Fi network\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21285","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21289","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Interception (active eavesdropping) between two systems ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21285_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Interception (active eavesdropping) between two systems\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si21300","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21304","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Specific targeting of a Wi-Fi user luring them to click on a link ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21300_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Specific targeting of a Wi-Fi user luring them to click on a link\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16163","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_579","roles":{}},{"id":"si16187","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_80","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_81","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19375","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19389","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19705","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19718","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19733","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19746","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19761","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19774","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19789","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19802","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16211q1","for":"Slide16211q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_576","title":"Correct - Answer: C  MITM attack intercepts a signal and acts as a proxy between two communications, masking itself to look identical to the Wi-Fi landing page.  Considered ‘active eavesdropping’, it collects your private data such as passwords and banking or credit card information and is widely used by hackers in Wi-Fi cafés and on unsecured networks.  Keep this in mind when you are using internet hotspots outside of the office or home and be cautious of what you access.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_577","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  MITM attack intercepts a signal and acts as a proxy between two communications, masking itself to look identical to the Wi-Fi landing page.  Considered ‘active eavesdropping’, it collects your private data such as passwords and banking or credit card information and is widely used by hackers in Wi-Fi cafés and on unsecured networks.  Keep this in mind when you are using internet hotspots outside of the office or home and be cautious of what you access.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16157","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_578","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16211","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_176","si16077","si16092","si16103","si21289","si21304","si16187","si16201","si19375","si19389","si19705","si19718","si19733","si19746","si19761","si19774","si19789","si19802","si16157"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16211"},"question":{"interactionId":"16057","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2. What is a Man-in-the-Middle (MITM) attack?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_177","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_177","roles":{}},{"id":"si16375","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_594","roles":{}},{"id":"si16272","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_581","title":"3.  A Pineapple device is a type of a MITM attack that: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_582","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16287","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_583","title":"Intercepts the ‘beacon’ sent from your wireless device looking for Wi-Fi connections ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16283_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"329","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intercepts the ‘beacon’ sent from your wireless device looking for Wi-Fi connections\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_584","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_585","title":"Auto-harvests your beacon addresses and adds them to a pool of targets ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16294_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"331","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Auto-harvests your beacon addresses and adds them to a pool of targets\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21319","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21323","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Creates a Wi-Fi ‘honeypot’ that can read your credentials in plain text ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21319_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Creates a Wi-Fi ‘honeypot’ that can read your credentials in plain text\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21334_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_593","roles":{}},{"id":"si16393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_82","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16407","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_83","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19403","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19417","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19817","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19858","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19873","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19886","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19901","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16417q2","for":"Slide16417q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16339","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_590","title":"Correct -Answer: D  The Pineapple device has evolved making it even easier to hijack your signal where you are vulnerable to many types of tricks and attacks.  Not only can it ‘see’ what you are typing, it can redirect your traffic to a spoofed website where you expose your sign-in credentials to your favorite social media site, health care portal or confidential network.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16351","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_591","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  The Pineapple device has evolved making it even easier to hijack your signal where you are vulnerable to many types of tricks and attacks.  Not only can it ‘see’ what you are typing, it can redirect your traffic to a spoofed website where you expose your sign-in credentials to your favorite social media site, health care portal or confidential network.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16363","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_592","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16417","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_177","si16272","si16287","si16298","si21323","si21338","si16393","si16407","si19403","si19417","si19817","si19830","si19845","si19858","si19873","si19886","si19901","si19914","si16363"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16417"},"question":{"interactionId":"16252","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3.  A Pineapple device is a type of a MITM attack that:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_178","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_178","roles":{}},{"id":"si16536","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_604","roles":{}},{"id":"si16455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_595","title":"4.  What do you call a rogue device connected to your wireless network? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_596","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_597","title":"Wireless Intruder ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16466_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"338","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Wireless Intruder\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16477","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_598","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16481","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_599","title":"Rogue Ransomer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16477_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"340","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Rogue Ransomer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17449","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Cyber Surfer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17445_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cyber Surfer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si18501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18505","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Beacon Hacker ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18501_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Beacon Hacker\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16530","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_603","roles":{}},{"id":"si16554","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_84","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16568","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_85","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19431","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19445","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19929","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19942","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19970","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19985","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19998","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20013","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20026","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16578q3","for":"Slide16578q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16500","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_600","title":"Correct -Answer: A  Your network may be supporting one or more Wireless Intruders from a relatively benign or accidental ‘bandwidth borrowing’ neighbour to a hacker looking to exploit your resources.  Ensure you have a WPA2 encrypted router with a strong password and consider engaging further wireless network protection (see next question).  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16512","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_601","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A  Your network may be supporting one or more Wireless Intruders from a relatively benign or accidental ‘bandwidth borrowing’ neighbour to a hacker looking to exploit your resources.  Ensure you have a WPA2 encrypted router with a strong password and consider engaging further wireless network protection (see next question).  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_602","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16578","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_178","si16455","si16470","si16481","si17449","si18505","si16554","si16568","si19431","si19445","si19929","si19942","si19957","si19970","si19985","si19998","si20013","si20026","si16524"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16578"},"question":{"interactionId":"16435","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4.  What do you call a rogue device connected to your wireless network?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_179","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_179","roles":{}},{"id":"si16697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_614","roles":{}},{"id":"si16616","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_605","title":"5.  How can you prevent a ‘Bandwidth Borrower’ or malicious ‘Wireless Intruder’? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_606","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16631","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_607","title":"Ensure you have encryption and strong password protecting your router ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16627_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"343","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Ensure you have encryption and strong password protecting your router\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16638","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_608","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16642","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_609","title":"Monitor connected devices to your Wi-Fi through your router administration ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16638_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"345","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Monitor connected devices to your Wi-Fi through your router administration\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21357","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Engage a bandwidth watcher or IP scanner tool with an intrusion alert ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21353_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Engage a bandwidth watcher or IP scanner tool with an intrusion alert\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21368","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21372","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21368_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16691","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_613","roles":{}},{"id":"si16715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_86","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16729","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_87","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19459","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20041","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20054","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20069","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20082","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20097","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20110","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20125","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20138","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16739q4","for":"Slide16739q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16661","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_610","title":"Correct - Answer:  D  Even with a strong password and encryption, you may have one (or many) intruders on your wireless network.  The easiest way to prevent this is to frequently change your router password (on your router administration page).   There are also many wireless watcher or IP scanning tools that can be downloaded (some for free) to warn you when a rogue device has or is connected.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16673","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_611","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  D  Even with a strong password and encryption, you may have one (or many) intruders on your wireless network.  The easiest way to prevent this is to frequently change your router password (on your router administration page).   There are also many wireless watcher or IP scanning tools that can be downloaded (some for free) to warn you when a rogue device has or is connected.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16685","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_612","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16739","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_179","si16616","si16631","si16642","si21357","si21372","si16715","si16729","si19459","si19473","si20041","si20054","si20069","si20082","si20097","si20110","si20125","si20138","si16685"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16739"},"question":{"interactionId":"16596","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5.  How can you prevent a ‘Bandwidth Borrower’ or malicious ‘Wireless Intruder’?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_180","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_180","roles":{}},{"id":"si16858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_624","roles":{}},{"id":"si16777","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_615","title":"6.  I should feel comfortable using hotel wireless as it is secured and restricted     to guests only. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_616","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16792","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_617","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16788_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16799","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_618","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16803","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_619","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16799_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si16852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_623","roles":{}},{"id":"si16876","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_88","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16890","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_89","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19487","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20153","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20166","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20181","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20194","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20209","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20222","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20237","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20250","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide16900q5","for":"Slide16900q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16846","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_622","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21378","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Correct - Answer:  B  Using secure hotel Wi-Fi is fairly low-risk when browsing for local restaurants and entertainment; however, they generally do not have security experts on staff.  There are security features that need to be enabled for a network and patches that need to be regularly installed to manage malware or vulnerabilities.  Always use caution when using any public wireless network.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21382","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  B  Using secure hotel Wi-Fi is fairly low-risk when browsing for local restaurants and entertainment; however, they generally do not have security experts on staff.  There are security features that need to be enabled for a network and patches that need to be regularly installed to manage malware or vulnerabilities.  Always use caution when using any public wireless network.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide16900","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_180","si16777","si16792","si16803","si16876","si16890","si19487","si19501","si20153","si20166","si20181","si20194","si20209","si20222","si20237","si20250","si16846"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide16900"},"question":{"interactionId":"16757","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6.  I should feel comfortable using hotel wireless as it is secured and restricted     to guests only.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_181","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_181","roles":{}},{"id":"si17049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_636","roles":{}},{"id":"si16957","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_625","title":"7.  What it the most secure option to choose when logging onto a network to use Wi-Fi? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_626","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16972","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_627","title":"‘Private’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16968_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Private’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16979","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_628","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16983","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_629","title":"‘Home’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16979_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Home’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si16990","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_630","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16994","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_631","title":"‘Public’ ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si16990_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Public’\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":2}}}},{"id":"si18080","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18084","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"‘Group’  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si18080_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"‘Group’ \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17043","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_635","roles":{}},{"id":"si17067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_90","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17081","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_91","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19515","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19529","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20265","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20278","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20293","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20306","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20321","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20334","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17091q6","for":"Slide17091q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17013","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_632","title":"Correct - Answer:  C  By choosing ‘public’, the network assumes that you do not want to be ‘discoverable’ or share your files with anyone (like you may on a trusted private, home or work network); it defaults to the most secure settings by turning these options off (including Bluetooth).  Even if you have set up a ‘Homegroup’, it won’t be enabled on acomputer that is designated ‘public’.     Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17025","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_633","title":"Incorrect - Answer:  C  By choosing ‘public’, the network assumes that you do not want to be ‘discoverable’ or share your files with anyone (like you may on a trusted private, home or work network); it defaults to the most secure settings by turning these options off (including Bluetooth).  Even if you have set up a ‘Homegroup’, it won’t be enabled on a computer that is designated ‘public’.     Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17037","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_634","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17091","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_181","si16957","si16972","si16983","si16994","si18084","si17067","si17081","si19515","si19529","si20265","si20278","si20293","si20306","si20321","si20334","si20349","si20362","si17037"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17091"},"question":{"interactionId":"16937","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7.  What it the most secure option to choose when logging onto a network to use Wi-Fi?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_182","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_182","roles":{}},{"id":"si17225","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_648","roles":{}},{"id":"si17133","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_637","title":"8.  You can feel reasonably secure when using VPN at a Wi-Fi hotspot. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_638","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17148","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_639","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17144_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"360","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17155","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_640","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_641","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17155_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"362","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si17219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_647","roles":{}},{"id":"si17243","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_92","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17257","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_93","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19543","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si19557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20377","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20390","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20405","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20418","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20433","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20446","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20461","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20474","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide17267q7","for":"Slide17267q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17189","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_644","title":"Correct - Answer: A  Even though a hacker can intercept your signal and attempt to gain access to your information, the information will be encrypted and therefore unusable.  This should be the only instance that you would consider using a password-protected site as these sites store your credentials and allow access to sensitive information.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17201","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_645","title":"Incorrect - Answer: A  Even though a hacker can intercept your signal and attempt to gain access to your information, the information will be encrypted and therefore unusable.  This should be the only instance that you would consider using a password-protected site as these sites store your credentials and allow access to sensitive information.  Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si17213","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_646","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide17267","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_182","si17133","si17148","si17159","si17243","si17257","si19543","si19557","si20377","si20390","si20405","si20418","si20433","si20446","si20461","si20474","si17213"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide17267"},"question":{"interactionId":"17113","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8.  You can feel reasonably secure when using VPN at a Wi-Fi hotspot.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_183","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_183","roles":{}},{"id":"si20774","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_696","roles":{}},{"id":"si20682","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_680","title":"9.  The ‘Evil Twin’ is: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20693","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_681","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20697","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_687","title":"A wireless network that creates a copy of itself and sends it to your home router ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20693_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"360_388","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A wireless network that creates a copy of itself and sends it to your home router\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_688","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_689","title":"A device that copies information you enter on Wi-Fi and sends it to Facebook ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20704_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"362_389","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A device that copies information you enter on Wi-Fi and sends it to Facebook\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si20715","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_690","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20719","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_691","title":"A copy of yourself made on a 3-D printer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20715_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"390","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A copy of yourself made on a 3-D printer\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21411","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21415","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"An exact duplicate of a wireless network luring you to log into the counterfeit network instead of the real one ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21411_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"An exact duplicate of a wireless network luring you to log into the counterfeit network instead of the real one\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si20768","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_695","roles":{}},{"id":"si20796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_100","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_101","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20836","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20854","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20866","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20878","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20890","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20902","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20914","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20926","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20938","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20950","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide20963q8","for":"Slide20963q8"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_692","title":"Correct -Answer: D  The Evil Twin is masked to appear and act exactly like the Wi-Fi you were planning to connect to.  When you log in, you are actually logging onto the counterfeit site that proceeds to send all of your information to the hacker.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_693","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  The Evil Twin is masked to appear and act exactly like the Wi-Fi you were planning to connect to.  When you log in, you are actually logging onto the counterfeit site that proceeds to send all of your information to the hacker.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20762","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_694","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide20963","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_183","si20682","si20697","si20708","si20719","si21415","si20796","si20814","si20836","si20854","si20866","si20878","si20890","si20902","si20914","si20926","si20938","si20950","si20762"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide20963"},"question":{"interactionId":"20668","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"9.  The ‘Evil Twin’ is:\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_184","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_184","roles":{}},{"id":"si21088","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_708","roles":{}},{"id":"si20996","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_697","title":"10.  Apps from a reputable ‘app store’ are always safe to use on Wi-Fi. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21007","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_698","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21011","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21007_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"360_391","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si21018","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21022","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_701","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21018_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"362_392","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si21082","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_707","roles":{}},{"id":"si21110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_102","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_103","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21150","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_104","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21168","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_105","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21180","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21192","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21204","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21216","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21228","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21240","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21252","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21264","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide21277q9","for":"Slide21277q9"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21052","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_704","title":"Correct - Answer: B  Many third party apps are designed with the express purpose to collect user data and/or install malware unbeknownst to the owner of the device; that is why it is recommended to always procure your apps from a reputable ‘app store’ such as Google Play and Play Store.  Reputable companies have checks and policies in place that ensure a certain safety and quality in their product, however, even they do not guarantee that the app is safe to use.  There are still documented scams occurring within the best app stores and no app is safe to use if it is not kept up-to-date with patches to mitigate vulnerabilities.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_705","title":"Incorrect - Answer: B  Many third party apps are designed with the express purpose to collect user data and/or install malware unbeknownst to the owner of the device; that is why it is recommended to always procure your apps from a reputable ‘app store’ such as Google Play and Play Store.  Reputable companies have checks and policies in place that ensure a certain safety and quality in their product, however, even they do not guarantee that the app is safe to use.  There are still documented scams occurring within the best app stores and no app is safe to use if it is not kept up-to-date with patches to mitigate vulnerabilities.   Click anywhere or press ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si21076","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_706","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide21277","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","Image_184","si20996","si21011","si21022","si21110","si21128","si21150","si21168","si21180","si21192","si21204","si21216","si21228","si21240","si21252","si21264","si21076"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21277"},"question":{"interactionId":"20982","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"10.  Apps from a reputable ‘app store’ are always safe to use on Wi-Fi.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Image_185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_185","roles":{}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6059","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6091","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6055","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6087","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Accuracy: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_186","roles":{}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":" Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si1270","si6231","Image_186","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"August2018Quiz","class":"project","title":"August2018Quiz","children":["Slide4365","Slide12483","Slide16211","Slide16417","Slide16578","Slide16739","Slide16900","Slide17091","Slide17267","Slide20963","Slide21277","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide12483q0","Slide16211q1","Slide16417q2","Slide16578q3","Slide16739q4","Slide16900q5","Slide17091q6","Slide17267q7","Slide20963q8","Slide21277q9"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":100,"passScore":80}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4365","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide12483","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide16211","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide16417","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide16578","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide16739","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide16900","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide17091","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide17267","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide20963","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide21277","title":"Slide 11"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 12"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 13"}]}